<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Pili and Pitzi</title>
    <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi" />
    <updated>2023-02-19T22:26:30-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Talia V.</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi: Go to the Movie Theater</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-go-to-the-movie-theater.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-go-to-the-movie-theater.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:26:30-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were excited to go to the movie theater to watch the latest adventure movie. They invited some&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were excited to go to the movie theater to watch the latest adventure movie. They invited some of their friends, and everyone agreed to meet at the theater. Pili and Pitzi arrived early, got their popcorn, and found their seats in the middle of the theater. As they were settling in, they noticed some kids talking loudly and running around the theater.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi remembered that it's important to be respectful in public places, especially when others are trying to enjoy something. They didn't want to spoil the movie experience for everyone else, so they politely asked the kids to quiet down and reminded them that people were trying to watch the movie. The kids apologized and the theater became quiet again.</p>
<p>As the movie began, Pili and Pitzi were completely absorbed in the story. But a few rows behind them, they could hear a man talking loudly on his phone. Pili and Pitzi realized that not only was he disturbing the other moviegoers, but he was also missing out on the movie. </p>
<p>Later, after the movie, Pili and Pitzi's friends arrived, and they all went out for ice cream. They discussed how annoying it is when people talk during a movie and how it ruins the experience for everyone. Pili and Pitzi pointed out that it's important to show respect to others and to be mindful of the way our behavior affects those around us.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi's friends agreed and mentioned other places where it's important to be quiet and respectful, like during presentations, in class, or in places of worship. They talked about how they would try to be more mindful of their own behavior in the future.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi  learned that being aware of others' needs and feelings is a key part of being a good member of the community.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-3 md:gap-4 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible"> </div>
<div>The End.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Keep Clean</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-keep-clean.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-keep-clean.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:23:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were spending a lovely day together in the jungle, when they noticed a rather unpleasant smell. They&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were spending a lovely day together in the jungle, when they noticed a rather unpleasant smell. They looked around to try and find the source of the odor, but couldn't seem to identify it.</p>
<p>As they were wandering, they stumbled upon their friend, a skunk named Skippy. Skippy greeted them with a smile, but Pili and Pitzi could barely stand the stench. They tried their best to hide their discomfort, but they couldn't help but wonder if Skippy was aware of his odor.</p>
<p>Pitzi turned to Pili and whispered, "Do you think we should tell Skippy about his smell?"</p>
<p>Pili replied, "I think we should. Maybe he doesn't realize how bad it is."</p>
<p>They approached Skippy and said, "Hey Skippy, can we talk to you for a moment?"</p>
<p>"Sure," Skippy replied. "What's up?"</p>
<p>Pili spoke up, "We wanted to talk to you about your hygiene. We couldn't help but notice that you have a strong odor."</p>
<p>Skippy looked embarrassed and replied, "Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't realize it was that bad."</p>
<p>"It's okay," Pitzi said. "But it's important to pay attention to your hygiene. Bad hygiene can make it difficult for people to be around you."</p>
<p>Skippy nodded in agreement and thanked Pili and Pitzi for bringing it to his attention. He promised to take a shower before going out again in the future.</p>
<p>From that day on, Skippy made sure to clean himself regularly, and Pili and Pitzi could tell the difference. They enjoyed spending time with him even more, now that the stench was gone.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi learned that paying attention to your hygiene is important, not just for your own health and well-being, but also for the comfort of those around you. They made a promise to always take good care of themselves, and to gently remind their friends to do the same.</p>
<p>As they walked through the jungle, Pili and Pitzi breathed in the fresh, clean air, and talked about the different ways they take care of their personal hygiene. Pili explained that elephants love taking mud baths to clean themselves, but they also make sure to take a shower with water and soap to get rid of any remaining dirt. Pitzi, on the other hand, explained that mice love to groom themselves by licking their fur clean. They also make sure to brush their teeth regularly to keep their breath fresh and their teeth healthy. Pili and Pitzi agreed that taking care of their personal hygiene was not only important for their health, but also for making a good impression on others. </p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-3 md:gap-4 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible"> </div>
<div>The End.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Throw a Party</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-throw-a-party.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-throw-a-party.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:16:42-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were very excited for Pitzi's birthday party. They had been planning and preparing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were very excited for Pitzi's birthday party. They had been planning and preparing for weeks to make sure everything was just perfect.</p>
<p>On the day of the party, Pili and Pitzi woke up early to start getting everything ready. They blew up balloons, set up decorations, and prepared the food. They were so excited to see all of their friends and celebrate Pitzi's special day.</p>
<p>As the party was scheduled to start at 1:00pm, Pili and Pitzi expected their friends to start arriving soon after. However, 1:00pm came and went, and no one had arrived yet. Pili and Pitzi started to worry that their friends wouldn't show up at all.</p>
<p>As the minutes ticked by, Pili and Pitzi started to feel more and more sad. They had put so much effort into the party and they just wanted their friends to be there to share it with them.</p>
<p>Finally, about half an hour late, their first friend arrived. Pili and Pitzi were so happy to see him, but they were also a little upset that he was so late. They tried not to show it and welcomed him warmly.</p>
<p>One by one, their friends arrived, each of them later than the last. Pili and Pitzi were happy to see each of them, but they couldn't help feeling disappointed that no one was on time.</p>
<p>After the last guest arrived, Pili and Pitzi thanked everyone for coming and handed out party hats and noisemakers. They all sang "Happy Birthday" and enjoyed some delicious cake and ice cream. Pili and Pitzi were happy that their friends had come, but they couldn't shake the feeling that it would have been even better if everyone had been on time.</p>
<p>As the party came to an end and their friends started to leave, Pili and Pitzi gathered them together. They thanked them for coming and told them how much they appreciated it, but they also explained how they had felt when everyone was late. They explained how important it is to be on time, especially when it's for a special occasion.</p>
<p>Their friends apologized and promised to be on time in the future. Pili and Pitzi forgave them and they all hugged each other goodbye. Pili and Pitzi were happy to have celebrated Pitzi's birthday with their friends, but they also learned a valuable lesson about the importance of being on time.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi made sure to always be on time, whether it was for a party, school, or anything else. They didn't want to disappoint anyone the way they had been disappointed on Pitzi's birthday. And whenever they invited someone to an event, they made sure to stress the importance of being on time, so that everyone could have the best possible experience.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-3 md:gap-4 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible"> </div>
<div>The End.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Return What They Borrowed</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-return-what-they-borrowed.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-return-what-they-borrowed.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:12:34-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were excited to explore a nearby cave in the jungle. As they packed their bags, Pili remembered&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were excited to explore a nearby cave in the jungle. As they packed their bags, Pili remembered something important.</p>
<p>“Pitzi, do you remember the last time we borrowed that backpack from our friend Hati? We never returned it,” Pili said.</p>
<p>“Oh, no! You’re right. We need to go return it before we go on our adventure,” Pitzi replied.</p>
<p>So, the two friends made their way to Hati’s house to return the borrowed backpack. When they arrived, Hati was happy to see them but also surprised.</p>
<p>“Pili, Pitzi! It’s so great to see you! What brings you here today?” Hati asked.</p>
<p>“We came to return the backpack we borrowed from you. We’re sorry we kept it for so long,” Pili said.</p>
<p>Hati smiled and said, “It’s no problem at all, but thank you for bringing it back.”</p>
<p>As Pili and Pitzi left Hati’s house, they felt relieved and proud of themselves for being responsible and returning what they had borrowed.</p>
<p>As they made their way to the cave, they couldn’t help but think about how important it is to always return things you’ve borrowed. It’s not only polite, but it shows that you are responsible and can be trusted.</p>
<p>Once they arrived at the cave, Pili and Pitzi made sure to take good care of their own backpack and avoid damaging anything in the cave. They explored the cave carefully and made sure to leave it just as they found it.</p>
<p>As they made their way out of the cave, Pili and Pitzi were happy and fulfilled from their adventure. They knew that by returning things they borrowed, they could continue to go on more adventures and make more memories with their friends.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi made sure to always return things they borrowed. They understood that being responsible and trustworthy was important, not just for them but for everyone they interacted with.</p>
<p>The end.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi&#x27;s Manners Lesson: Always Flush the Toilet</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzis-manners-lesson-always-flush-the-toilet.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzis-manners-lesson-always-flush-the-toilet.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:06:51-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    One sunny day in the jungle, Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were playing outside when they needed to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>One sunny day in the jungle, Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were playing outside when they needed to use the bathroom. They walked to the public restroom and saw that someone had left the toilet unflushed and the seat up. Pili and Pitzi looked at each other and frowned.</p>
<p>"That's not very polite," said Pili.</p>
<p>"Yeah, it's not fair for the next person who needs to use it," added Pitzi.</p>
<p>They both knew that they should always flush the toilet and put the seat down. It was just good manners.</p>
<p>As they were washing their hands, Pili and Pitzi noticed a sign on the wall that said "Please flush the toilet and put the seat down."</p>
<p>"Look Pitzi, the sign says the same thing we were just talking about," said Pili.</p>
<p>"Yeah, it's important to be respectful of others who need to use the bathroom too," said Pitzi.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi always made sure to flush the toilet and put the seat down whenever they used the bathroom, whether at home or in public places. They also made sure to remind others to do the same.</p>
<p>By being considerate of others and following good bathroom etiquette, Pili and Pitzi showed that they were not only polite, but also respectful and kind. And that's what good manners are all about!</p>
<p>The end.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Get Ice Cream</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-get-ice-cream.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-get-ice-cream.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T22:04:18-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were walking to their favorite ice cream shop when they noticed an older couple walking towards them&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were walking to their favorite ice cream shop when they noticed an older couple walking towards them struggling to open the door of the shop. Pili quickly ran to the door and held it open for the couple. They smiled and thanked him as they walked in.</p>
<p>Pitzi had noticed how happy the couple looked and realized how something as small as holding the door could make a big difference in someone's day. As they entered the ice cream shop, they saw that it was packed with people, and Pili and Pitzi realized that this could be a great opportunity to help people.</p>
<p>As they walked through the shop, Pili held the door for people coming in and out, while Pitzi tried to help people carrying heavy items. Pili and Pitzi's kind actions didn't go unnoticed, and soon people were thanking them left and right.</p>
<p>After they had gotten their ice cream, they noticed a little girl struggling to reach a napkin on the counter. Pitzi quickly ran to her and handed her a napkin, and the little girl smiled in gratitude.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi felt so good helping people that they continued to hold the door and help anyone who needed it. As they walked out of the ice cream shop, they realized that being polite is not just about holding the door for someone, it's also about showing kindness to others and making a difference in their day.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi made it a habit to hold the door for others and to help people whenever they could. They knew that even a small act of kindness could make someone's day better, and that made them feel happy and proud.</p>
<p>As they walked home, Pili turned to Pitzi and said, "Helping others makes me feel good inside. I hope we can do it again sometime." Pitzi smiled and replied, "Me too, Pili. It's important to show kindness to others, and holding the door for them is such an easy way to do that."</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi continued to practice this act of kindness everywhere they went, and soon it became a habit. They found that holding the door for others not only made them feel good, but it also made others feel happy and appreciated.</p>
<p>The End.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Share</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-share.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-share.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T21:59:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were having a great time in their classroom. They were learning about animals and nature, and the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were having a great time in their classroom. They were learning about animals and nature, and the lesson was so much fun.</p>
<p>After a while, Pili's stomach began to grumble. "I'm getting hungry," he said to Pitzi. "Are you hungry too?"</p>
<p>Pitzi checked her lunchbox and smiled. "I have a lot of grapes today," she said. "And you?"</p>
<p>"I have a peanut butter and jelly sandwich," Pili said.</p>
<p>The two friends went to the cafeteria to eat. They sat down at a table and began to unpack their lunches.</p>
<p>As they ate, they noticed that their friend Ella was sitting alone at a nearby table. She looked sad and didn't have any lunch with her.</p>
<p>Pitzi felt bad for Ella and whispered to Pili, "Hey, let's offer her some of our food."</p>
<p>Pili nodded in agreement, and they walked over to Ella's table. "Hey Ella, do you want some of our lunch?" asked Pili.</p>
<p>Ella smiled and nodded gratefully. "Thank you so much," she said.</p>
<p>Pitzi shared some of her grapes with Ella, and Pili shared his sandwich. They all chatted and laughed together while they ate.</p>
<p>After they finished eating, Ella thanked Pili and Pitzi for their kindness. "You guys are such good friends," she said.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi felt happy knowing they had made Ella's day a little bit better. They also learned that it's always a good idea to offer to share your food with someone who may not have any.</p>
<p>The next day, Pili and Pitzi came to school with extra snacks in their lunchboxes. They made it a habit to share their food with anyone who was hungry and alone at lunchtime. They even encouraged their other friends to do the same.</p>
<p>Their kindness and generosity soon became contagious, and soon many other students in the school were sharing their food and making new friends.</p>
<p>Pili and Pitzi were proud of what they had started. They knew that a small act of kindness can go a long way.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi made it a point to always offer to share their food, especially with those who were less fortunate. They knew that it was the right thing to do, and it made them feel happy and fulfilled.</p>
<p>The end.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Excuse Me, Pili and Pitzi!</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/excuse-me-pili-and-pitzi.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/excuse-me-pili-and-pitzi.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T21:49:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili and Pitzi were on a picnic in the park. They had just finished a delicious meal of bananas and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-rjskr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili and Pitzi were on a picnic in the park. They had just finished a delicious meal of bananas and peanuts when Pili let out a loud burp. Pitzi was surprised and a bit embarrassed by the sound.</p>
<p>"Pili, that was really loud and a little bit rude," said Pitzi.</p>
<p>Pili was taken aback. "I'm sorry, I didn't mean to be rude," he said. "I just had a lot of peanuts."</p>
<p>"It's okay, Pili," said Pitzi. "But next time, try to remember to cover your mouth when you burp. And if it happens again, just say 'Excuse me'."</p>
<p>Pili nodded and promised to be more careful. He didn't want to be rude or make Pitzi feel uncomfortable.</p>
<p>A few minutes later, Pitzi let out a big sneeze. "Achoo!" she exclaimed.</p>
<p>Pili quickly remembered the lesson Pitzi had just taught him. "Bless you, Pitzi," he said. "And don't worry, you don't need to say 'excuse me' when you sneeze. It's just a natural reflex."</p>
<p>Pitzi smiled and thanked Pili for his kind words. They finished their picnic and headed back home, making sure to be mindful of their manners along the way.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-3 md:gap-4 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible"> </div>
<div>The End.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Use Their Indoor Voices</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-use-their-indoor-voices.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-use-their-indoor-voices.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T12:35:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were best friends who loved spending time together. One day, they were invited&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-vbudk-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-vbudk-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were best friends who loved spending time together. One day, they were invited to a party at their friend's house, and they were very excited to attend. They dressed up in their best outfits and set out for the party.</p>
<p>When they arrived, they found that the house was filled with their animal friends, and everyone was having a great time. However, Pili quickly noticed that Pitzi was speaking very loudly and it was starting to get hard to hear each other over the noise.</p>
<p>Pili leaned over to Pitzi and whispered, "Pitzi, I think you're speaking too loudly. Can you try to use your indoor voice?"</p>
<p>Pitzi was a little embarrassed but agreed with Pili. "Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't even realize I was being loud. I'll try to speak more softly from now on."</p>
<p>Pili thanked Pitzi and together, they made an effort to use their indoor voices and set an example for the other animals. But, some of their friends were still speaking too loudly, so Pili and Pitzi politely reminded them to use their indoor voices.</p>
<p>"Excuse me," said Pili. "I don't mean to interrupt, but it's getting pretty loud in here. Would you mind speaking a little more softly?"</p>
<p>Their friends were surprised at first, but they quickly realized that they had been speaking too loudly and began to adjust their volume.</p>
<p>As the night went on, the party became much more enjoyable for everyone, and they could hear each other speak without any difficulty. Pili and Pitzi felt proud of themselves for helping to create a more comfortable and pleasant atmosphere at the party.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pitzi made a conscious effort to use her indoor voice when she was indoors. She realized that speaking too loudly not only made it difficult for others to hear, but it could also be seen as rude. Pili was proud of Pitzi for making the effort, and the two friends continued to have fun and enjoy their time together in a considerate and polite way.</p>
<p>The End.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pili and Pitzi Show Gratitude</title>
        <author>
            <name>Talia V.</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-show-gratitude.html"/>
        <id>https://hex20dec.github.io/piliandpitzi/pili-and-pitzi-show-gratitude.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-19T12:03:32-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were the best of friends. They had a lot to be grateful for,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-vbudk-79elbk h-full dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-vbudk-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col items-center text-sm dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="w-full border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 group bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="text-base gap-4 md:gap-6 m-auto md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-2xl xl:max-w-3xl p-4 md:py-6 flex lg:px-0">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex flex-col items-start gap-4 whitespace-pre-wrap">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Pili the elephant and Pitzi the mouse were the best of friends. They had a lot to be grateful for, and they knew it. One day, Pili woke up early in the morning and decided to take a walk in the jungle to enjoy the fresh air.</p>
<p>Pitzi was still sleeping when Pili left, so Pili decided to take the time to thank God for everything she had in her life. She looked around at the beautiful jungle and felt overwhelmed with gratitude.</p>
<p>"Thank you, God, for this beautiful jungle, the fresh air, and the warm sun," Pili said. "Thank you for my wonderful friend Pitzi and for all the other animals that call this jungle home."</p>
<p>As she continued her walk, she thought about all the other things she was thankful for, like her family, her health, and the food she had to eat. She knew that she was blessed in so many ways.</p>
<p>When Pili returned to her home, she found Pitzi awake and ready to start the day. Pitzi asked Pili where she had been, and Pili shared her experience of thanking God for everything she had.</p>
<p>Pitzi thought that was a great idea, so they decided to start their day by thanking God for everything they had.</p>
<p>"Thank you, God, for this beautiful day," Pitzi said. "Thank you for my wonderful friend Pili and for all the adventures we get to have together."</p>
<p>"Thank you, God, for our home, our food, and our health," Pili said. "And thank you for all the amazing opportunities we get to experience."</p>
<p>As they finished their morning prayer, they both felt a sense of peace and contentment. They knew that no matter what the day would bring, they were grateful for all they had.</p>
<p>From that day on, Pili and Pitzi made it a habit to start each day by thanking God for everything they had. They knew that even in tough times, there was always something to be grateful for, and that gratitude would help them to have a more positive outlook on life.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
